What's the right thing to do?
It's not like there's a right thing to do.
Like I've already said,
let's just forget everything
- and start over.
- Let's just start from scratch.
But she can't keep approaching people
by saying things like, "You're handsome."
How long are we supposed to wait
for her to change?
How are we meant to believe what she says?
That makes things easier for you,
but it'll only make us panic.
I know I made a big mistake
with how I tried
to get closer to you guys. Mmm.
And I guess I thought that was normal.
But I know now that it's not.
It might be difficult to do it right now,
but if you just do it little by little…
BO (27)
COMMERCIAL PAINTER
…I really think you need to just
- put in the effort to change how you act.
- Mmm-hmm.
Otherwise, if you keep saying,
"I don't know, I can't,"
then you'll never change.
But just remember this.
I know that we might have
hurt you today, okay?
But I was hurt too.
"Who are you most interested in?"
"Ma-kun. 'Cause you look like my ex."
But that sentence, "You're the guy
I'm most interested in, Ma-kun,"
you didn't say it
'cause you were interested in me.
It was just 'cause
you wanted to be friends.
MA-KUN (28)
MMA FIGHTER
That hurts.
- Huh?
- That was rude, the way he said that.
- He didn't have to say it like that.
- They're just making Maririn look worse.
So you're just saying I'm crazy.
- That's not it at all.
- No one's saying that.
- We never said that.
- Nobody's saying that.
- That's not it.
- I'm not being negative.
She's trying to do something about it.
RURU (26)
MODEL
- Is it that funny?
- Let's focus on moving forward from now.
'Cause, like, right now, we're just
complaining about what happened.
So I think we should talk about
what we're gonna do from now on.
I'm stepping out.
Ruru.
BAR OWNER
- Can I go check on her?
- Yeah, of course.
We're like family,
so we should be there for each other.
But the guys aren't thinking like that,
especially Kazuma.
But I do know what he's saying is true.
But when I saw him laughing,
it really pissed me off.
- I get that.
- Same.
Everybody has trauma.
We all grew up in a similar environment,
so we should understand each other,
or at least some of
what Marina is telling us.
We each have our traumas,
which have shaped how we live.
Like, we get it.
So why don't we try to understand that?
I thought being here
would finally show me what love is.
- But I don't know what to do anymore.
- Mmm.
But there's no right answer, is there?
This is just how you are.
You know, everybody's different.
We have different personalities.
And these different people
are gathered here.
HIKARU (23)
HOSTESS
So it's really wrong of them
to attack your personality.
And even though I was crying like that,
they still said they couldn't understand.
I get it, but it's not like I'm crying
because I want to.
- I just can't stop once I start.
- Hmm.
I usually stay quiet 'cause I'm scared.
But today…
…I thought I'd try to explain it,
- and I thought I did, but then Kazuma…
- Yeah, I know.
…may have felt offended.
I really didn't like the way
Ma-kun was acting, either.
- He was shutting the conversation down.
- Totally. I was like,
"You think you're acting like a man?"
They're eating.
Look at them by themselves,
eating together in their room.
I guess we should talk about it together.
- Emergency quest.
- Thank you.
If I'm being honest, what you said,
Kazuma, and I'm sure you all agree,
it was totally right.
I know you took the time
to consider everyone's feelings
and spoke for all of us.
We may not be able to reset things,
but, hey, like,
let's try to completely erase
the image of Maririn
that we all have. Got it?
- I'll try.
- It was like we were being grilled
without them hearing
both sides of the story.
Know what I mean?
- Mmm.
- And I really didn't like that.
Right? So I just asked
what we should do from now on.
- Mmm-hmm.
- If that makes them hate me, so be it.
But we can't just reset things.
We can't start from scratch.
Yeah, but we agreed to try
to do that, so isn't trying good enough?
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
Time to eat, everybody.
If the guys can all come
to terms with this
and then they come apologize today,
that's the best thing they could do.
Your breath stinks!
- Sorry.
- Bro, your breath stinks!
Like, don't talk.
What are they laughing about?
Did you shit your pants?
No. Come on. Let's go to the backyard.
- I'm going.
- You've got this.
Ruru is always so cool.
I find it so impressive
that she can just go off on her own.
We heard how much you guys were laughing.
So I guess you're done talking.
'Cause you were laughing so hard.
That's because they were teasing me.
Yeah, okay, I get it.
Like, once you were all done talking,
it makes sense that you guys
would start talking about normal stuff.
But from our perspective,
think about it, like,
hearing you guys laugh isn't funny at all.
Especially after our conversation,
where you guys were kind of
rejecting Marina's personality.
Like, "This is what we think."
Isn't that wrong?
All of us met here, right?
We're like family, right? We're friends.
But I thought you guys
didn't want to understand her.
So, what was the point
of our conversation?
Well, to be honest, Ruru,
I think we were trying to be considerate
by not talking about it.
- No…
- That's how I felt.
I think you guys
should've talked about it more deeply.
Seeing as you had the chance
to talk among yourselves.
For Marina,
there's nothing to be happy about,
so it's not nice hearing you guys laugh.
You thought it was considerate,
but we haven't come to an agreement yet.
- So it's not okay to be laughing.
- Yeah, we have.
- No, we haven't.
- What? Yeah, we did.
Right at the end, we asked,
"What should we do?"
We said we'd forget about it and move on.
But I said that
we can't just forget about it.
- Hmm.
- But we said we would try.
- Mmm-hmm.
- So we agreed on that.
Okay, but just so you know,
among the girls,
we don't see that as an agreement.
- Look, that's all I wanted to say.
- Okay. Got it.
That's it.
Leo, I'm sorry,
but I can't stand how Ruru was just now.
I know it was brave to put herself
in the firing line, but still.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RAPPER FROM SAGAMIHARA
SPITTING LYRICS OF PURE LOVE
ARI
KAWASAKI'S IT-GIRL HOSTESS
OUT TO FIND A REAL MAN
HIKARU
KYOTO BAR OWNER
GOING ALL-IN FOR HIS WOMAN
NANIWA'S BARROOM BEAUTY
LOOKING FOR TRUE LOVE
MARIRIN
KURUME YANKII
WHO GREW UP BEHIND BARS
BO
EX-YAKUZA MMA FIGHTER
LOOKING FOR HIS RIDE-OR-DIE
MA-KUN
NAGOYA'S NO.1 HOSTESS
WHO PUTS MEN IN THEIR PLACE
ASSUN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST
WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
AN HONEST MODEL
IN SEARCH OF LOVE
RURU
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
NO FILTER KICKBOXER
FROM MIYAGI
HA-CHAN
EX-NO.1 HOST
CHASING TRUE LOVE
KAZU-KUN
BUDDHA LEAN
Kazuma.
GIRL'S ROOM
Asuka, Ruru, can we talk?
Could we put the Marina thing to the side?
What I want to talk about is…
Like, honestly,
I just want to resolve this tension
between the boys and the girls.
Mmm.
That's why I want to talk.
- A boss meeting.
- I know.
A summit meeting.
Uh, Ruru, the way you came into the room
and started talking earlier,
or the way you started talking earlier,
I thought it was a little…
uh, out of line.
Mmm.
After all the guys listened
to what you said…
- Mmm.
- …some of them may have thought,
"So, we just have to put up
with everything?"
Mmm…
- To be honest, I thought that too.
- Mmm.
- That was…
- But--
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
But, you know, I'm also the kind of person
who gets emotional and talks.
So I was worried
I wouldn't be able to talk properly.
But, you know, we all met here
and we've become sort of like a family.
- Hmm.
- And the idea was for us to find love
in this group.
So I wanted you guys
to have more sympathy towards Marina.
Her trauma is too recent.
- That's the way she feels too.
- Mmm.
She can't just change
how she feels straight away.
So I wanted you guys
to sympathize with her more.
And then we heard you all laughing.
- So I felt very emotional when talking.
- Mmm.
And, Asuka?
Same for me.
You haven't talked at all.
Seriously?
I really feel like
I want to drop out right now.
You want to drop out
after this conversation?
Hmm, yeah, I do still.
Why?
No, let's not change the subject.
So, what should I do?
No. I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
I just suddenly hated everything,
and didn't want to see anybody.
It was like something had…
had snapped inside of me.
I just wanted to drop out.
I was done, you know?
It made me want to throw it all away.
I really don't know how I feel anymore.
A different problem has come up.
Hold on, what are we watching?
This is a dating reality…
- A dating reality show, okay?
- A show, okay.
- That's what we're watching, Nagano.
- Right, but the dating part…
doesn't seem to be on the table anymore.
There's a rift
between the men and women right now.
How has this happened?
I mean, we've been watching them
the whole time.
It's amazing.
- Assun.
- She said she wanted to drop out.
- Hmm.
- So now another problem has come up.
- And it's the first time, right?
- Yes.
That somebody on the show
has wanted to drop out.
Yes, it is.
I think that she must have been
feeling extremely upset by it all.
But, I mean,
this is a really difficult situation.
- Hmm.
- I think it's because…
- …everybody has their own,
you know, trauma and their own pain.
- So we've got some people saying…
- I see.
…"Let's use this show to fix our hearts.
Otherwise, we'll never be able
to fall in love,"
while others just want to move forward.
- Right.
- They want love.
- Hmm.
- There's not much time.
- Exactly.
It's a battle between these two sides.
- Wow.
- Yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
LOVE DINER
What are we making?
What shall we make?
What are we eating?
Bo just guesses the amount
of rice he puts in the measuring cup.
What's the point of using it?
So rice.
Right. Carrots and…
A car?
No way! What?
- You've gotta be kidding.
- Our idol!
- Right? Yeah, potatoes…
- Yeah.
And these?
MR. HENTONA
Hey, everybody!
My God!
- Ma-chan!
- What?
- Mr. Hentona!
- No way!
Hentona!
He always comes at the right time.
Hey, guys!
- Oh, the bananas!
- Oh, bananas!
I brought bananas. I wanted to see you.
- Give me half.
- Check this.
- So good.
- Delicious, right?
- The most delicious I've ever had.
- It is.
- Yeah. Uh, wait.
- So good!
I was worried about you guys,
but y'all look like you're good.
- We're doing well.
- Thank you so much, Mr. Hentona.
You look a little down.
He noticed right away!
- I'll tell you later.
- Oh, okay.
The other day, you were…
You were the only one
who didn't look happy.
So I was worried.
I see. Well, thank you.
All right.
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
- It is.
- Yeah.
So, that day at the banana farm,
you said that
- a man who is abusive is no good.
- Uh-huh.
All the men I've dated have been abusive.
I was wondering, like,
how do I meet someone who isn't like that?
- Hmm.
- I find it so hard.
Even though I've, you know,
been alive for 60 years…
- Hmm.
- …I still fail all the time.
But, you know, failure is…
- Aren't you afraid of failing?
- …Half-- No.
- You fail 'cause you take on challenges.
- Hmm.
- Right?
Taking on a challenge
means you're halfway to success.
- It's not a failure.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Understand? Yes.
- It's important to challenge yourself.
So, all of the experiences
that you've had with men,
all of the men you've met,
all of them have been abusive, right?
- These become life experiences for you.
- Hmm.
So, eventually, you'll be able to tell,
"Oh, this type of guy
is probably abusive."
- Hmm.
- I also want to make sure
- I tell the guys this. You know?
- Yeah.
Your looks and appearance
are just given to you by your parents.
- Hmm.
- They're from birth.
And we should be grateful for that.
You should be grateful to your parents.
But we create our inner selves.
Hmm. Well, I'm half Japanese,
so I have a mixed background.
And I've always been bullied
because of the way I look.
My mom, kind of…
Well, she abandoned me.
And my dad, well,
he's always lived overseas, so…
- I've never lived with my parents.
- Mmm.
And since I don't have parents around,
it's like I'm searching for love
I don't know.
The past is the past.
- It's over.
- Hmm.
But it also lives on in the future.
You've had a hard time, you know?
In other words,
the fact that
you didn't receive much love,
- that's also an experience.
- Hmm.
And when you yourself become a mother,
I think you'll be a good mother
who can give more love
than your mother did.
- Mmm-hmm.
- You'll give as much as you've suffered.
I'm really worried that
since I didn't grow up in a loving home,
it could mean that if I have a kid…
if I have a kid,
I won't be able to love them,
because I wasn't taught.
- Hmm.
- So, first, you have to love yourself.
Like I said,
the fact you were born into this world
is already a miracle in itself.
And by chance,
you were able to come to Okinawa.
- Yeah.
- This is also like fate.
- Hmm.
- All these things, one by one,
will make up your life experiences.
It sounds positive
when you put it that way.
- Hmm.
- Like, I feel like I can be positive now.
- Yeah, you can.
- I used to wonder if my negativity
was just caused
by everything from my past.
You said you can't change the past,
but you can change the future.
- You can change it, you can.
- I'm so glad I got to talk to you.
- Thank you, Mr. Hentona.
- Of course.
So that's why you should
just go ahead and do…
- Yeah. I'll do that.
- …what you want to do.
After talking to you, Mr. Hentona,
I feel like I'm not really that scared
of failing anymore and stuff like that.
- Hmm.
- I've got a lot more courage.
You'll be fine.
- Just remember all your experiences here…
- Hmm.
…and feel free to come back.
- I understand.
- Anytime.
- I'll come back if something bad happens.
- Of course.
And I'll say, "Welcome back."
Nobody's ever said "welcome back"
- to me before.
- Oh, really?
It feels like I have a home
for the first time.
Come anytime.
You're free to do anything.
You can do anything.
- Yeah. Thank you so much.
- Okay?
- And if you get really tired…
- Yeah.
- …come back here.
- Okay, got it.
I want to choose love.
I want to become stronger.
I want to tell everybody how I feel.
I want to be loved, even if I'm like this.
And I came here to find love,
no matter what form it takes.
Like, I want to be friends with everybody.
If you take a step, you're halfway there.
I want to trust that,
and then it'll help me move in my own way.
'Cause this is who I am.
Four days until the confessions.
Today, the weather is good,
so we have prepared a barbecue.
At the barbecue,
please deepen your relationships together.
It's chilly.
- Let's eat. I'm hungry.
- I have something.
- Can I go first?
- Yeah, sure.
- I'll go first.
- Yes.
Let her speak.
I'm sorry about the fact
that I couldn't talk properly yesterday
because I was crying.
And, like, the things you all said to me,
I totally get why you said them,
and, like, I want to try to make a change.
I'm going to try, but I'd also
like you all to meet me halfway.
So can you please be friends with me?
- Okay!
- All right!
- Of course, we'll meet you halfway.
- I want to say something too.
When I went to the guys' room,
I was kind of confrontational.
And I wasn't considerate of your feelings
when I talked to you guys.
So I'm sorry that I made you feel upset.
- It's okay.
- Please be friends with me.
- Hey, be friends with us too.
- We'd love to be friends.
- We want to be friends.
- Let's do it.
- Let's grill this meat.
- Great.
She's great at apologizing.
Huh?
Does anybody want something to drink or…
- Oh, wow, crab!
- Here we go. Boom!
It's too peaceful.
- It's burning.
- Shit, it's already charred black!
- Oh, this is bad.
- What are you doing?
- I'm supervising.
- Oh.
- They're smiling again.
- Yeah.
- Wow, that's amazing!
- Yeah, I know.
Hey, the tide is low today.
Oh, my God, this might be good.
Let's play catch.
Here I go.
Oh, my God, I'm scared.
Hey, if…
If we don't catch it,
we'll get wet, right?
Here I go!
Oh, my God.
- Looks fun.
- That's sweet.
You know when we talked
in the living room yesterday?
Uh-huh, yeah.
It made me realize
something about you, Hikaru.
How do I say this?
At first, I didn't like
how cautious you were.
Like, I was thinking,
"We don't have much time left,
you gotta make a decision."
But then, Maririn said
she wanted to get to know everyone,
so she told them
she was interested in them.
When she said that, I was like,
"I'd actually hate it if Hikaru tried
to get to know people that way."
Like, I'd hate it if you told everyone
you were interested in them,
or, like, if you touched them.
So now I actually think
it's an amazing thing
that you're taking your time
and you're being cautious.
Like, I think that's much better.
- I didn't realize that before, but--
- So you realized that because of Maririn?
I did, yeah.
I wrote something.
Hey, where did you…
- That letter…
- I brought this from home.
The paper's different, right?
Yeah, so I brought this paper from home
- to write a letter to someone special.
- You brought it?
Are you laughing?
DEAR HIKARU
WASSUP?
THIS IS MY THIRD LETTER,
BUT I WROTE AGAIN BECAUSE
I WANTED TO TELL YOU HOW I FEEL
Mmm-hmm…
What do you mean, "Mm-hmm…"?
Everybody's just using the school's paper.
But I wanted to write my letter
to someone special on my own paper.
They say that this paper brings happiness.
- You don't like it?
- No, it's the best.
- The best?
- Yeah.
It's the best.
You feel fired up?
- Can I give you a kiss?
- You're going too fast!
Come on, it's fine.
Are we allowed to smoke here?
Oh, so you can sit here.
- You good? You tired?
- Hmm?
- Are you tired?
- Yeah.
Hmm, I thought so.
- I'm the oldest one here.
- Hmm.
I've to look at the bigger picture
and think about more things.
Yeah, I guess so.
I thought,
"Whatever, it's too much trouble."
Hmm, I get it.
But I'm more mature than you,
so you don't have to be so uptight.
I'm probably more mature.
- Really? You think that?
- Yeah.
Did you calm down?
- Yeah, after I slept.
- Mmm.
- Let's switch gears.
- Yeah, okay.
- We don't have much time.
- For real.
You see how important sleep is?
That's what it is.
- They just gave us a lesson.
- Yeah.
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
Have you decided?
- Um… It's hard, yeah.
- Hard, right?
What about you?
- I see.
- Something here too?
- I might have changed.
- Oh, really?
You've changed how?
- I've had a change of heart.
- Mmm.
I didn't think my feelings would change.
Oh, you mean from when you first arrived?
Yeah, in the past few days.
- Oh, really? Mmm.
- Mmm.
What is it? Like, did something happen?
- Yeah, something happened.
- I see.
Wait, so you feel like
you might have decided?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
- Mmm.
I've decided.
Ruru.
What?
Based on that reaction?
It's a customer interview.
"I've decided. I'll take Ruru."
- Like she's a product.
- It's Ruru.
- You can't say that.
- Thinks he'll get next-day delivery.
Her face, her strong personality,
how she doesn't hide anything,
and how she takes action right away.
I just really like all of that.
Excuse me for intruding, Leo.
Don't underestimate the baby of the group.
- One, two, three. There you go.
- Thanks.
I'm a little sticky.
- Isn't this amazing?
- Wow. It's beautiful.
We always see
this ocean at night, don't we?
Mmm, that's true.
- I like it better now.
- Yeah, it's nice.
Leo, you also want to get married
before you're 30, right?
Hmm.
So, like, I'm here to find somebody
who's thinking about the future.
And I'm pretty sure
that you and I have the same mindset.
Dating someone
who isn't thinking about marriage yet
would be a waste of time.
- And you know I love kids, right?
- Mmm.
My brother is eight years younger than me.
I used to give him baths
and change his diapers.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
To be honest, I also really like kids.
After I graduated high school,
I started training to teach kindergarten.
- And I did that for two years.
- Mmm.
But then, I realized I wanted
to be a model, like, straight away,
so I decided to give it a try.
So I haven't worked as a teacher yet,
but I had some practical training
at the vocational school.
When I went to a children's home
for the training…
Mmm.
…there were kids living there
who didn't have a mom.
But when I went to preschool
and kindergarten for training,
- the kids all had moms.
- Mmm.
And they would come
pick them up from school,
and I could feel that
they were being loved as they grew up.
But at the children's home,
it was completely different.
- Mmm.
- I mean, like,
they were all pretty closed off.
And, like, they didn't know
how to express their feelings.
Like, one of the kids even hit me.
Yeah.
But, like, I wanted to accept
that part of them too.
- There was an elementary school boy.
- Hmm.
And this one time,
when he was having a tantrum,
he said something like,
"I wish I was never born."
And I felt that, like,
although that innocent school kid
had done nothing wrong,
this world that we live in
had somehow made him feel that way.
So I think that, like, rather than being
a preschool or kindergarten teacher…
I mean, it's just sort of
a dream right now,
but, one day,
I would really like to build a…
a children's home, you know?
Where I can be a sort of second mom
to all the kids there.
- That's amazing.
- You see, I also really like kids.
- There's only four days left.
- Yeah.
And, yeah, I would really like
to go on a date with you.
- Will that happen?
- I'll make it happen.
- So, maybe if you can win a date…
- Oh, I definitely will.
Leave it to me.
- Leave it to me.
- Mmm.
- I've got this.
Leo can actually
say things like that, though.
- You're such a girl.
- No, no, no.
That's a nice atmosphere.
- Everyone's more positive.
- Yeah.
You know,
I've talked about my abusive past.
Oh, honestly,
don't worry about that anymore.
No, I just mean…
I just wanted to tell you
that you can change
- because I was able to change.
- Mmm-hmm, yeah.
- I was in jail for a long time, you know?
- Mmm-hmm.
- I was in jail for a long time…
- Mmm.
…but, well, it's only been a year
since I got out.
- And I'm trying to do my best.
- Mmm.
So, well, about six months
after I got out,
- I was living on my own.
- Mmm.
I was told that not many people
live on their own
and be independent…
Well, sort of independent,
- six months after getting out.
- I can imagine.
So, I'm trying to change,
you know, little by little.
- Mmm-hmm.
- So I said that to you yesterday
because you can definitely do it.
- I'm glad I met everyone here.
- Mmm.
I actually think it's kind of like fate.
There's only four days left
and it's getting intense.
So how do you feel, Bo?
Well, yeah…
Um, things are gonna get fun.
- Things are gonna get more fun.
- More fun?
Oh, man. My brain is about to explode.
- I'm having so much fun every day.
- Go ahead and explode.
Here I go. Okay.
Okay, here I go.
Guys, we only have four days left.
So let's keep being badly in love
until the end.
Okay, ready?
Hey, wassup!
- Okay!
- Yay!
- That was great.
- Well done.
- The best!
- Good for them.
- The ethics class is over.
- They got through the big problem now.
- They got through it.
- So from now on…
- Yeah.
…it's Badly In Love.
- It can go back to Badly In Love.
- We're getting there. At last!
- We're back.
- Ethics class is…
- It's over.
- …over.
- All right!
- Thank you for waiting.
- The dating show is starting.
- It's starting.
Hey, what about Mr. Hentona's entrance?
Our hero.
I mean, Mr. Hentona
came at exactly the right time, didn't he?
It was perfect.
I think he had a really
profound effect on Maririn.
Look at that incredible smile here.
- Right?
- I know.
- And then at the barbecue…
- Hmm.
…she was the first to raise her hand
and then she apologized.
And everyone responded straight away.
- Straight away, yeah.
- They said "okay" instantly.
Because she did things the right way.
- The right way?
- The right way.
- She did, yeah.
- She apologized.
- Yeah.
- That's all it takes.
And then, Ari gave Hikaru a letter.
And so now,
the love has started there again,
- Right, sensei?
- It's rekindled.
But again, we don't know what Hikaru meant
when she said she was happy, do we?
She read the letter,
and then she had this huge reaction like…
- Yeah.
- Right? It was big.
And then, we have Ruru's reaction.
Tai-chan was like, "I don't really know."
I don't think she noticed.
She was like,
"Oh, you changed your mind? Really?"
- She doesn't get it at all.
- She doesn't get it.
- You think she has no idea?
- Yeah.
That's the face of someone
who has no idea.
Ruru didn't have any romantic intentions
when she went over there to talk to him,
- like, there was no deeper meaning.
- He should know from experience.
- I wanted him to notice that.
- Yeah.
LOVE DINER
- Hey there.
Did I get my feelings across?
- What feelings? What?
- Huh?
- I told you I changed my mind, right?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
I was wondering
if I got my feelings across.
I didn't think you were talking about me.
Yeah, after narrowing it down,
there's only you left in my head.
So you don't have any feelings
for Hikaru anymore?
Mmm, my feelings for Hikaru…
- kind of come and go.
- Mmm.
You're gonna get told off again.
- By Ruru.
I'm the type of person
who enjoys being in love,
- and wants to be in love.
- Hmm.
But I'm 26 now,
and I want to get married before I'm 30.
- Yeah. That makes sense.
- Yeah.
So I don't really want to date somebody
just because I have feelings for them.
Hmm, I think that's right.
I want to be realistic
and see if I can be with this person
for the long haul,
and make a relationship work.
I think about that a lot.
Well, as you know,
I'm a hairstylist, and I'm in Tokyo.
Okay, well, if you have feelings for me,
I want you to give me
everything you've got.
- Yeah.
- Know what I mean?
I do…
…have feelings for you.
I have feelings for you.
Well, like I said, I like people
who really express their emotions.
- Right?
- I want to talk to Leo too.
- Right.
- Because I haven't decided yet.
Mmm.
I'll do my best. Just more.
- Thank you.
See you later.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, he's totally in.
- Spellbound.
- Looks like he's in love.
- Right?
It hit the sweet spot. Full swing.
How much do I like her out of 100?
About 1,000.
I fell in love with her with that hug.
She smelled good.
I didn't want to let go of her then.
I think I broke through today.
I honestly think that my time has come.
I thought Ruru was nice
because she was from Tokyo.
But she kept talking based on
her own preconceptions and standards.
- Like last night.
- Hmm.
- She said that yesterday.
- Stuff like that.
- It was all based on emotions.
- Hmm.
Nothing goes well
when you talk too emotionally.
Hmm. You're actually surprisingly
pretty logical, aren't you?
That's right.
But I shouldn't be like that.
Ma-kun is good at talking.
- Hmm.
- But I just can't do that.
- I don't mean to be intense…
- Hmm.
…but I want to talk about things
one by one and solve them.
Like, "If this happens, let's do this.
And if this happens, then let's do that."
"That's not good,
so then, we should do this."
I hate wasting time on things
that don't solve the root of the problem.
- It's inefficient. Yeah.
- Hmm.
I want someone
who understands what I say. Yeah.
- Men are stupid, you know.
- Hmm.
- Always changing their minds.
But women…
they stick to their decision
once they've made it.
Yeah, that's true.
And we make decisions quickly.
- Mmm. Right?
- Yeah.
Men can be weak-minded.
Always, like, "What should I do?"
It's amazing how you can get so into it.
Well, I've made up my mind.
Women are more manly than men.
I've always thought that.
This is definitely
a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
- Yeah.
- So we should throw ourselves into it.
Like, I thought Ruru was nice,
but I only know her through other people.
Yeah, I don't know
what kind of person she is.
- Hmm.
- So…
So I thought it was important to just
let go of it all and try talking to her.
Hmm. You're right.
Will you put in the effort?
Yeah, I think I can.
This was an important first step.
Like, for me.
- Hmm.
- I mean, this type of conversation.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yeah.
- You took a step forward.
- Thank you.
- Hmm.
I thought
I wanted to talk to Ruru. You know?
You don't get many opportunities
to be on a show like Badly In Love.
And meeting someone from Tokyo,
whose base of operations
is so close to mine,
it's also kind of like fate, no?
I really like Ruru's smile.
My favorite thing to do
is watch her from behind
while she's laughing
and watching TV or something.
And the reason I do that is because
I like girls who laugh out loud.
I really want to honor
this kind of fate and destiny,
and I want to tell her
that I want to believe in it.
It's a kind of…
It's not persuasion,
but it's a kind of pick-up line.
I'll use that kind of thing
to gradually make it more realistic.
If I have more opportunities with her,
I'll succeed.
- Ruru, let's talk.
- Sure.
- We talked a little bit in the sauna.
- Mmm.
I think we've had
the most opportunities to talk.
- Mmm.
- Right.
That's why, like, after all of that,
the fact that
you're set on Leo is kind of…
I mean, it's not like I'm angry about it,
but I do feel kind of lonely.
- Mmm.
- Yeah. Like, "What?"
Well, I try to be realistic, you know?
- Hmm.
- I think really deeply about things.
He's in Kyoto, and I'm in Tokyo.
I'm not made for long-distance.
Personally.
Not being able to see each other
when you want to, it's like…
Right. Yeah, I really think that.
But I think it's impossible for me
to be with anyone else.
- Mmm.
- I want to have a realistic relationship.
I want to have a proper relationship
when I leave here.
- We're the only ones in Tokyo, aren't we?
- Yeah, that's right.
That's something I think about,
and it's a huge thing for me.
I have the money
to take the bullet train anytime.
So I could go see him,
but I have limited time.
And I have work, too.
So when I think about that reality…
I start thinking, "That's not gonna work,"
and I start to doubt.
So I'm the only one.
That's true.
Well, distance-wise, that's true.
Before I came here,
as long as I could move my thumbs,
I would tell girls how I felt with a text.
I'd tell them half-heartedly,
and they'd kind of accept it,
and I had a lot
of half-hearted relationships.
But being here,
I have to look them in the eye, you know?
I have to look them in the eye
and tell them how I feel,
and I have to keep telling them
how I feel.
Otherwise, if I do things half-heartedly,
it's not that I think I'd lose,
but I don't think
that they'd accept my feelings.
So I think I've changed.
I look them in the eye now.
And I tell them
how I feel with my actual words.
I believe that doing things that way
is very important and also very powerful.
So I thought I'd talk to you.
I don't know about your past,
so I wanted to ask you about that.
My past isn't anything special,
to be honest.
I got arrested at the end
of my first year of junior high.
For what?
- 'Cause I got into a fight.
- Okay. Mmm.
They assessed me.
And the first time, I just got sent back.
I came back.
Then, about a year later,
I got arrested again.
- For fighting? Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
And then, I went
to the juvenile training center.
I came back at the end of the third year,
three months
before graduating junior high.
Then six months later,
I was back at the center.
Hey, you know,
I've actually been violent
in the past as well.
Yeah?
I got into fist fights
with my ex and stuff.
Did you ever regret it afterwards?
Like, after you were ever violent?
I did regret it.
Or I don't know if it was regret.
- More like a reflection?
- But I did reflect on it.
I mean, it's like…
You gotta think
about the future a little more.
When you start dating people
at this age, you know?
Yeah, you don't wanna be with someone
who's gonna get arrested.
Yeah, for real.
Yeah, that's exactly it.
If they go to prison,
you can't, like, just ask them
what they're thinking whenever you want.
- And you can't see them when you want.
- Yeah.
You also feel bad
for making the other person wait.
But that bit was my fault, so…
Everyone who gets arrested says that.
"Everyone who gets arrested says that."
- As if it's something really common.
- It is a common thing.
So, if the two of us were to start dating,
I would want you to know
that you can't do those things
because I'm here.
For sure. I don't want to get arrested.
Not that I want to do anything bad.
But also, you have to accept
the bad parts too.
- That's how I think a relationship works.
- I get it. To what extent? Okay.
It's easy to notice the bad parts
more than the good parts.
- That's true.
- Which means that you fight more often.
When you're dating, that's how it is.
So then you just have to think about
how you can change that.
They understand each other.
I want to cherish the person
closest to me.
- Bo never talks this much.
- You're right, he doesn't.
It's all about compassion.
I want someone who's really deep.
Well, I'm deep.
Really?
- You said you're deep.
- I'm deep.
- Nice.
- Good.
Hmm.
In my past relationships,
I always wanted someone I could rely on.
Someone who understood me
and accepted every part of me.
That's what I thought when I was dating.
But it was a total failure.
Because they always ended up lying to me.
They'd say that
they hadn't done anything illegal.
I'd ask them to swear to me.
They'd swear to me,
but then they'd end up in prison.
They'd tell me
that they'd already divorced their wife.
But then I'd find out they hadn't.
I think that through this experience
we've had in here,
Bo's apologized honestly and sincerely,
and I see that.
I don't think that he lied.
If he's lied, then I won't be able
to trust anyone again.
Well, I think that every time.
That's how much I truly believe
that Bo wouldn't lie.
I don't think he would.
I think he's the one I trust the most
out of the guys.
'Cause, you know,
he also shows you his bad side first.
That's why I think he wouldn't lie.
If I had to choose,
it would be Bo.
That's great.
It seems like
her feelings are already set.
A bento box.
- What's up?
- Oh, you're late.
Oh, what is it?
- Well, I wanted to talk.
- Okay.
- So, what--
- I made you a bento.
- No way! Seriously?
- Yeah.
- No way!
- They're so cute.
I've never made a bento box
for a guy before.
That's crazy. It's hot! Thank you.
- How nice.
- Can I eat this?
- Yeah. Have you eaten?
- No, not yet.
Thanks for the food.
They look really good together.
- Yeah.
- Simply put.
Mmm.
- It's delicious!
- Is it good?
- Glad to hear that.
It's really good.
I didn't even taste it.
I didn't have time.
Yeah, it's so good. Like, so, so good.
- So you've never done this before?
- Never.
- It's your first time? Very first time?
- It is. Uh-huh.
This is actually so great. Oh, my God!
- Ma-kun is so cute, isn't he?
- Right?
- It's unexpected.
- Yeah.
I mean, I've made bento boxes before,
but I just ate them all myself.
- Mmm.
- I've never made one for someone else.
Mmm. Yeah, it's delicious.
Really, really good.
It's so warm.
Seriously.
- Thank you. It was so delicious.
- Of course.
Well, I know I've said this before,
but regardless of whether or not
we continue after this experience here,
if we can't continue this relationship,
I don't want to be in a relationship.
I don't want it if it's not real.
- Hmm, I understand.
- Hmm.
Is that okay?
It sure is.
What?
- But it was so out of the blue!
- So casual.
Sneaking a nice little daytime kiss.
- But then again, Mr. Ichiro says…
- Oh, I get it now!
So it means that her judgment
wouldn't have been affected.
Exactly.
I'm embarrassed!
I feel so embarrassed!
Oh, that was a delicious bento.
BRING ON LIFE
- Sensei, go ahead.
- Go on, Sensei.
Okay, everyone, please put your right
and left hands together like so.
Wassapetit.
- Wassapetit!
- That's a new one.
Is the ajillo good?
- Yeah.
- It's okay now?
- I'm glad.
- You couldn't eat it before, could you?
- Why not? Is it the taste?
- This is the only thing I don't like.
- Wait, what?
- I actually hate carrots.
- I don't like yuzu.
I mean, I can eat it, but I don't.
It's time for the evening sauna session.
We have prepared for you…
…a two-day and one-night date
that starts tomorrow.
Yes, please!
It's a sleepover.
Have we done that before?
- No.
- We haven't, have we?
The men will have a serious showdown.
The winner will then choose
- the woman he's interested in.
- What do they mean?
The game we will play
will be a real test of guts for the men.
Sounds like this test
needs to be won by a real man.
So is this showdown thing tomorrow?
- Yeah.
- They'll tell us more then.
I'm sure I'll win.
Piece of cake.
I don't know what it is, but still.
I'm gonna win.
When we had our talk,
Ruru said that if there was a date,
she'd like to go with me.
So I'm going with Ruru.
I think tomorrow is gonna be a big event
that will change everything.
If I win tomorrow, I'm choosing Ruru.
And I'm going for the win.
Hikaru.
I said that if I win, I'd take her.
I really want to get a kiss. Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna win.
And the person I want to go
on the overnight date with is Hikaru.
I'll do what I have to do.
But it's down to Asuka.
- A sleepover.
- What was that?
- This is huge. Going to be fun.
- Two days and one night means…
Tomorrow night is the night they mean.
Oh, yeah?
Excuse me.
- Huh?
- Wait, what? "Excuse me"?
Listen up, please,
I have something to tell you.
- Whose voice is that?
- That voice!
- Sensei? Right?
- Yes. It's him.
- It's been a while.
- Huh?
Huh? What's happening?
A school rule has been broken.
My heart is pounding.
I need to talk with all of you
about this rule violation.
Huh? I don't get it.
What?!
What is this?
- I'm so sorry, guys.
- There's more?
- That's enough!
- Yes.
Can I be honest with you? I'm tired.
For real.
Huh?
- Sorry.
- That was really scary.
- It was, right?
- I was like, "Who is that?"
So, in Season 1…
- Right!
- The person who came then?
- The one called Yanboh…
- Yeah.
- …was actually Director Kimura.
- I see.
We really didn't think he would have
to make an appearance this time.
I thought so too.
But then, with only three
or four days left…
I see, Mr. Kimura…
We're the ones who are tired here.
- Mr. Kimura must be the most tired.
- The whole staff.
Yeah, but he's the most tired.